[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Retsina, sometimes referred to as the wine of the Gods, is produced in which country?", "correct_answer": "Greece", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "France", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Everyone in the town of Rock Ridge, featured in Blazing Saddles, had the same surname. What was it ?", "correct_answer": "Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Smith", "Peters", "Taylor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Swedish botanist and physician, considered one of the fathers of modern ecology, initiated the method of binomial classification.", "correct_answer": "Carolus Linnaeus", "incorrect_answers": ["Alfred Nobel", "Nils Gabriel Sefstrom", "Johan August Arfwedson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is Coach Patches OHoulihan killed in the movie Dodgeball?", "correct_answer": "A large sign from inside the casino falls on him.", "incorrect_answers": ["His wheelchair battery shorts out and electrocutes him.", "He is assassinated by MeShell.", "He is run over by a car trying to dodge traffic."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award did the 2002 movie The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers win?", "correct_answer": "Best Visual Effects", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Picture", "Best Director", "Best Editing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The average lifespan of a box turtle is about 20 years.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1959 mystery movie North by Northwest?", "correct_answer": "Alfred Hitchcock", "incorrect_answers": ["Stanley Kubrick", "None of these", "Milos Forman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these flamingo species is not native to the Americas?", "correct_answer": "Lesser Flamingo", "incorrect_answers": ["Chilean Flamingo", "Andean Flamingo", "James Flamingo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the actor who was honored with the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for 1986.", "correct_answer": "Prince for Under the Cherry Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["Emilio Estevez for Maximum Overdrive", "Sylvester Stallone for Cobra", "Sean Penn for Shanghai Surprise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A turtles upper shell is called the plastron.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 8 Mile, which one of B-Rabbits friends shot himself in the leg by mistake?", "correct_answer": "Cheddar Bob", "incorrect_answers": ["Future", "Sol", "DJ Iz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual application does ground nutmeg have in India?", "correct_answer": "It is smoked.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is used as a fertilized for pot plants.", "All of these", "It is used to make dyes."]}]